myrealgames.com 2019-12-11

# 

## 1\. Introduction

MyRealGames.com is committed to providing an entertaining service. MyRealGames.com is a property of My Real Games Limited. MyRealGames.com respects the privacy concerns of visitors to MyRealGames.com. This privacy statement describes how we collect and use the personal information you provide on our website.

## 2\. Information we collect

As is true of most websites, we gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-through data. We use this information, which does not identify individual visitors, to analyze trends, to administer the website, to track visitors movements around the site and to gather information about the geographic location of our visitors as a whole.

MyRealGames.com may request and/or collect personal information from you on a voluntary basis when you send questions or comments via e-mail to our customer support. The requested information may include personal information such as your name and e-mail address. If you are under the age of 13, you will need your parent or guardian's consent before you can provide any personal information to us using e-mail/contact form. By allowing you to send e-mail to us, we are not attempting to collect any personal information about you. We will only use personal information (such as name and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Although we may retain your e-mail for a period of time, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific inquiry or comments.

## 3\. Cookies

A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. MyRealGames.com may use cookies to improve the use of our websites. However, we do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.

## 4\. Collection of Information and Third-Party Sites and Sponsors

We use Google and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served. MyRealGames.com may provide links from our Web sites to third party Web sites and we encourage our users to read third party sites privacy policies before submitting personal information. MyRealGames.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the content of third party sites.

## 5\. Internet Safety

MyRealGames.com strongly recommends that Parents take time to communicate and educate their children about Internet Safety.

## 6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

You agree that MyRealGames.com may change this Privacy Policy at any time. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes.

## 7\. Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please use our contact form.

All trademarks are the property of their respective owners. All Rights Reserved.
